fly4free.com 2005-04-04

# Travel Newsletter Travel Smart

| 

[Airfare Within Canada  
Airfare To Caribbean  
](http://www.smarttraveler.com/online.html)Int'l Airfare From USA  
Int'l Airfare From Canada   

**Travel Services**  

[  
TRAVEL INSURANCE  
FOREIGN CURRENCY](http://www.travelex-insurance.com/index.asp?LOCATION=09-6029)

**Travel Links**  
Airlines  
Airports   
Cruise Lines  
Tour Operators  
Bus Companies    
Trains   
Accommodations

Safe to Sail!  

Online Business Review  
Places we've been and used - good or bad!  

* * *

Simply add your e-mail in  
the box above and submit!  
It's that easy!  
**PRIVACY POLICY**

Make 2003 Special   
Get your internet presence!   
Only $299.00!  
INCLUDING .com, .net, .biz, .info, or .name DOMAIN NAME*& 1 YEAR HOSTING!  
*Based on availability  

SELL DREAMS!!!  
EARN COMMISSIONS!!!  
CRUISE THE WORLD!!!  
Become a [  
Home Based Cruise Agent](http://www.homebasedcruiseagents.com/)

Extra | Extra | Extra

**Curious as to your heritage?**  
Try the World heritage site. Filled with information on all parts of the world

**Need a dinner recommendation?** Anywhere?   
Go There->  
**  
Want to know what's going on over _there_?** Travel news available daily.  
Go There->

**International Airfares, Domestic Airfares or Last Minute Airfares?** Visit our helpful agent affiliates at Smarttraveler.com [  
Go There->](http://www.smarttraveler.com/)

**America Under Attack**  
One New Yorker's Story  
Tuesday September 11, 2001 D DAY - by Fran Capo  
<Read More>  

**Cruises  
1-866-546-2929**  

* * *

**Movie Reviews  
& Celebrity Interviews  

* * *

**A Tribute  
To Our Heroes**  
Visit: [A Tribute To Heroes](http://www.atributetoheroes.com/)

**This Week With...**  
[TheLighterSideOfTravel](http://www.thelightersideoftravel.com/) [  
Movie Reviews  
Celebrity Interviews  
](http://www.bluntreview.com/) [Cyber Sitcom](http://www.theestrogenfiles.net/)

**Helpful Sites**  
[Tax Deductable Cruising?  
](http://www.cruisenewsletter.com/tdcruise.htm)[eBay!](http://www.qksrv.net/click-820693-2202639)   
[SpaWish.com   
](http://www.qksrv.net/click-820693-45211) [Bath-and-Body.com](http://www.qksrv.net/click-820693-239545)  
EntertainmentLinks  
Todays News  
[Wine Charms](http://www.qksrv.net/click-820693-2681107) **Destination Info**  
[Maps  
](http://www.mapquest.com/)[Tourist Bureaus](http://www.towd.com/)  
Aruba  

**Worldwide Trivia**  
20 Questions  

**About TNL**  
Contacts  
Writers   
The Company  
 Advertise With Us   
Submissions

* * *

For the most complete listing of available tours anywhere!   
Including:

LAS VEGAS * HAWAII * ORLANDO * MEXICO * BAHAMAS * JAMAICA* EUROPE * AUSTRALIA * COSTA RICA & MUCH MORE!  

ATTENTION CVB'S

REACH 785,000+   
READERS AND   
PROMOTE AMERICA  
WITH OUR RED, WHITE & BLUE SPECIALS

FOR MORE   
INFORMATION:  

* * *

Want Travel Tips From the Pros? Check out our Travel Tips page. A quick list of what every traveler should know. [<Read More>](http://www.travelnewsletter.com/traveltips.htm)

* * *

**[GROUP CRUISE SPECIALS](http://www.groupcruises.info/)** Celebrate your family reunion, anniversary, wedding, school reunion aboard a cruiseship. Rates are low and fun is high!

* * *

IN LOVING MEMORY   
OF KODY BENGSTON

Our hearts weep for   
one too quickly   
taken from our lives.  
[Visit:  
ForOurChildren.org](http://www.forourchildren.org/)

| 

* * *

**Exercise Your Right As An American - Travel**   

* * *

SmartTraveler.com, Inc. takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

**NOTICE:[Click here](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/online/sitesee.htm) for important information about safe surfing from the Federal Trade Commission. **

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**  

  * This policy covers how SmartTraveler.com, Inc. treats personal information that SmartTraveler.com, Inc. collects and receives, including information related to your past use of SmartTraveler.com, Inc. products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that SmartTraveler.com, Inc. does not own or control, or to people that SmartTraveler.com, Inc. does not employ or manage. 

**Information Collection and Use**

      **General**  

  * SmartTraveler.com, Inc. collects personal information when you register with SmartTraveler.com, Inc., when you use SmartTraveler.com, Inc. products or services, when you visit SmartTraveler.com, Inc. pages or the pages of certain SmartTraveler.com, Inc. partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. SmartTraveler.com, Inc. may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 
  * When you register we may ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with SmartTraveler.com, Inc. and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 
  * SmartTraveler.com, Inc. collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of products and services that we offer. 
  * SmartTraveler.com, Inc. uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you receive from us and our partners, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * SmartTraveler.com, Inc. does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 
    * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with SmartTraveler.com, Inc. under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help SmartTraveler.com, Inc. communicate with you about offers from SmartTraveler.com, Inc. and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; 
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of SmartTraveler.com, Inc.'s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 
    * We transfer information about you if SmartTraveler.com, Inc. is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, SmartTraveler.com, Inc. will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 
  * SmartTraveler.com, Inc. displays and delivers targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, men ages 35-50 from a particular geographic area. 
    * SmartTraveler.com, Inc. does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. 
    * SmartTraveler.com, Inc. advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies). 

**Cookies**

  * SmartTraveler.com, Inc. does not now, but may in the future set and access SmartTraveler.com, Inc. cookies on your computer. 
  * SmartTraveler.com, Inc.does not now, but may in the future let other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to SmartTraveler.com, Inc.'s cookies. 
  * SmartTraveler.com, Inc. does not now, but may in the future use web beacons to access SmartTraveler.com, Inc. cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with SmartTraveler.com, Inc. products and services. 

**Your Ability to Delete Your Account**

      **General**  

  * You can delete your SmartTraveler.com, Inc. Account Information, including your marketing preferences, at any time. 
  * We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the SmartTraveler.com, Inc. service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the SmartTraveler.com, Inc. TravelNewsletter, that are considered part of your SmartTraveler.com, Inc. account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. 
  * You can delete your SmartTraveler.com, Inc. account by visiting our [Subscription Deletion](http://www.travelnewsletter.com/takemeoff.html) page. 

**Confidentiality and Security**

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 
  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. 
  * Your SmartTraveler.com, Inc. Account Information is password-protected. 
  * In certain areas SmartTraveler.com, Inc. uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

  * SmartTraveler.com, Inc. may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your SmartTraveler.com, Inc. account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

**Questions and Suggestions**

  * If you have questions or suggestions, please email us at [qands@smarttraveler.com](mailto:qands@smarttraveler.com) or you can contact us at: 

  * SmartTraveler.com, Inc. Inc.  
Customer Care - Privacy Policy Issues  
1128 Royal Palm Beach Blvd. #471  
Royal Palm Beach, FL 33411  
(561) 383-7486

---|---
